<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects | Academic</title>
    <link>https://academic-demo.netlify.app/project/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://academic-demo.netlify.app/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Projects</description>
    <generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://academic-demo.netlify.app/media/icon_hua2ec155b4296a9c9791d015323e16eb5_11927_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_3.png</url>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://academic-demo.netlify.app/project/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Measles Vaccination Analysis</title>
      <link>https://academic-demo.netlify.app/project/measles-vaccination/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://academic-demo.netlify.app/project/measles-vaccination/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;script src=&#34;https://academic-demo.netlify.app/project/measles-vaccination/index_files/header-attrs/header-attrs.js&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;


&lt;div id=&#34;low-vaccination-rates-and-high-personal-exemption-percentages-in-schools-may-contribute-to-increasing-the-odds-of-a-measles-outbreak&#34; class=&#34;section level1&#34;&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Low vaccination rates and high personal exemption percentages in schools may contribute to increasing the odds of a measles outbreak&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;amanda-l.-skarlupka&#34; class=&#34;section level2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Amanda L. Skarlupka&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;affiliations&#34; class=&#34;section level3&#34;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Affiliations:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Center for Vaccines and Immunology, Department of Infectious Diseases, University of Georgia, Athens, GA.
Abstract— (50 words)
Decreasing vaccination rates among school aged children are leading to an increasing incidence of the vaccine preventable childhood disease, measles. Decreasing vaccination and increasing personal exemptions may contribute to increasing the odds of measles outbreak. Medical exemptions were not found to potentially contribute. Limiting personal exemptions may decrease measles outbreaks.
Text—(1199 words)
Introduction
Measles is highly contagious and transmitted from coughing and sneezing and direct contact with infected individuals. Symptoms include fever, cough, runny nose and a characteristic rash. Non-immunized individuals have a 90% chance of contracting the disease when exposed [1]. The live-attenuated measles vaccine should be administered in two doses at 12 months and right before entering kindergarten, and is in combination with mumps and rubella as MMR [2]. The immunity is defined to be lifelong. The vaccine is considered safe, causing mild adverse reactions such as fever in 5-15% of the individuals, and a rash lasting 1-3 days in roughly 5% of the individuals [2].
Vaccine hesitancy and antivaccination movements contribute to decreased vaccination in schools and has been declared by the World Health Organization a threat to global health. This anti-vaccination movement is often spread and escalated through misinformation and social media [3]. Previously it has been determined that MMR vaccination reduces the incidence rate for that population [4]. But the overall vaccination rate in schools has decreasing since 2000 and the number of cases increasing up to 1282 cases in 2019 [5]. Therefore, it is important to maintain high proportions of vaccinated populations to limit disease transmission.
With the increasing percentages of school age children not being vaccinated due to medical and personal reasons. I aimed to understand how these increasing exemptions and decreasing vaccination rates effected the odds of a measles outbreak.
Materials and Methods
The data used for this study were gathered from two different sources. The vaccination were from the Wall Street Journal publication [6], available at &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/WSJ/measles-data&#34; class=&#34;uri&#34;&gt;https://github.com/WSJ/measles-data&lt;/a&gt;. The vaccination data covers the 2017-2018 school year for eleven states, and the other twenty-two states’ data are for 2018-2019. Rates and percentages were assumed to be similar from year to year. The school’s name, state, county, district, type, enrollment, MMR and overall vaccination rate, and separate percentages of students exempted from vaccination for medical, personal and religious reasons.
The United States case information was from the supplementary excel file from the Gardner (2020) article [7]. The case data is from the cases reported in the United States from during the year 2019. Data was initially gathered and collated from numerous sources including news reports, and state public health databases. All data was analyzed using R version 4.0.2 and RStudio [8].
Data from the continental United States was used for analysis. Variables that were incomplete or unnecessary were removed, including religious exemption, enrollment data, type, district, name, and index. County level rates and percentages were averages. Number of cases were shown in graphs as log base 10 transformed values. Statistical significance was defined as a p-value &amp;lt; 0.05.
Results
The cases from 2019 were not localized to a single state (Fig 1A). The number of cases ranged across the United States with the highest number of measles cases being in New York State (1072 cases). However, when looking at the data on a higher resolution (county level) it became clear that the cases were not evenly dispersed throughout a state (Fig 1B). Therefore, the data was analyzed at the county level to limit invalid state-level assumptions. For example, within New York state, the cases were centered around New York City. Washington and Oregon also had a high case count across the counties bordering the western coast.
The vaccination data was not available for all states. However, when looking at the vaccination data for measles, mumps, and rubella (MMR) vaccination specifically (Fig 1C), the percentage was consistently high across the available regions with an estimated mean value of 94.32% (n = 28,324 counties, 95% confidence interval (CI): 94.22%, 94.43%). The personal exemption percentages of the entire country had a mean of 6.93% (n = 6411 counties, 95% CI: 6.73%, 7.13%) (Fig 1D). The medical exemption percentages had a mean of 3.10% (n = 12,972 counties, 95% CI: 3.03%, 3.18%) (Fig 1E). The overall vaccination percent for the country was lower than that of the MMR vaccination coverage at a mean value of 92.0% (n = 26,243 counties, 95% CI: 91.88%, 92.13%) (Fig 1F).
After separating the vaccination data based on county, the most informative states that also had a high measles case load were Washington and Oregon. These two states were selected for further analysis to determine if there was any relation between vaccination rates and exemption percentages and case number. Figure 2 presents the exemption, vaccination, and cases for both Washington and Oregon.
Odds ratios were determined using factored continuous variables. The factor levels cutoffs were determined by the quantiles of the northwestern county data. After which the odds ratios were determined for the four quantiles compared to an outcome of presence of a cases. Each exposure was done separately (Table 1).
The highest overall vaccination coverage of 93-98% was used as the reference. The 89-93% overall coverage had 5.36 times higher odds of have a case, and the 83-89% had a 2.55 times higher odds of a case compared to the reference. The lowest vaccination coverage 53-83% had 0.89 time the odds of having a case. With a p-value of 0.113, the 89-93% overall vaccination coverage warrants further analysis. The highest MMR vaccination coverage of 95-100% was used as the reference. The 92-95% MMR coverage had 5.25 times higher odds of have a case, and the 89-92% had 3.23 times higher odds of a case compared to the reference. The lowest MMR vaccination coverage, 71-89%, had 1.76 times the odds of case.
For personal exemptions, the lowest percentage was used as the reference, 0.75-3%. The 3-5.4% percentage had an odds ratio of 6.02, and the 5.4-7.1% had an odds ratio of 3.45. The highest exposure, 7.1-29.2% had an odds ratio of 1.00. The p-values were not significant. However, the 3-5.4% group had the lowest p-value of the odds ratio of 0.086. This relationship along with the previous case of overall vaccination coverage should be investigated further. The medical exemption category 0-0.5% was used as the reference. The 0.5-2.0% group had an odds ratio of 0.64 and the 2-13.7% group had a ratio of 0.59, with non-significant p-values.
Discussion
No odds ratio was significantly different compared to the reference group. However, some of the groups were close to significant. The 3-5.4% compared to 0.75-3% personal exemption group had an odds ratio of 6.02 with a p-value of 0.086. Although this was not significant this indicates something further to look into. With only 73 cases in the two states and by creating four different factors the data may not be factored adequately. When comparing medical exemptions, there was no factor that was close to being significant. Thus medical exemptions may not contribute to the odds of a measles outbreak as much as personal exemptions.
Further analysis could include an additional analysis of the specific outbreak. Data including school enrollment numbers, population size, religious exemptions and population religion, may prove useful in future comparisons. Religious data would be insightful especially due to the 2018 outbreak in New York occurring in populations where vaccination is against religious belief [9, 10].
In conclusion, this research indicates that decreased vaccination coverage and increased personal exemptions may contribute to increased measles cases, but it does not implicate medical exemptions as a factor.
 
Author Bio
Amanda Skarlupka is a graduate researcher investigating the design of broadly reactive influenza vaccines. Her interests include immunology and data analysis.
References
1. CDC, Measles, in Epidemiology and Prevention of Vaccine-Preventable Diseases, J. Hamborsky, A. Kroger, and S. Wolfe, Editors. 2015, Public Health Foundation: Washington D.C. p. 22.
2. Rota, P.A., et al., Measles. Nat Rev Dis Primers, 2016. 2: p. 16049.
3. Dhaliwal, D. and C. Mannion, Antivaccine Messages on Facebook: Preliminary Audit. JMIR Public Health Surveill, 2020. 6(4): p. e18878.
4. Geier, D.A., J.K. Kern, and M.R. Geier, Childhood MMR vaccination and the incidence rate of measles infection: a ten year longitudinal cohort study of American children born in the 1990s. BMC Pediatr, 2019. 19(1): p. 325.
5. Sinclair, D.R., et al., Forecasted Size of Measles Outbreaks Associated With Vaccination Exemptions for Schoolchildren. JAMA Netw Open, 2019. 2(8): p. e199768.
6. Moriarty, D., T. Umlauf, and B. Abbot, What’s the Measles Vaccination Rate at Your Child’s School?, in The Wall Street Journal. 2019.
7. Gardner, L., et al., Persistence of US measles risk due to vaccine hesitancy and outbreaks abroad. The Lancet Infectious Diseases, 2020. 20(10): p. 1114-1115.
8. RStudio-Team, RStudio: Integrated Development for R. 2020, RStudio, PBC: Boston, MA.
9. Kennedy, A.M. and D.A. Gust, Measles outbreak associated with a church congregation: a study of immunization attitudes of congregation members. Public Health Rep, 2008. 123(2): p. 126-34.
10. Knol, M., et al., Large ongoing measles outbreak in a religious community in the Netherlands since May 2013. Euro Surveill, 2013. 18(36): p. pii=20580.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Address for correspondence: Amanda L. Skarlupka, Center for Vaccines and Immunology, Department of Infectious Disease, University of Georgia, 501 D. W. Drive, Athens, GA, 30602 USA; e-mail: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:skarlupka@uga.edu&#34; class=&#34;email&#34;&gt;skarlupka@uga.edu&lt;/a&gt;
 
Table 1. Odds ratio of Northwestern counties’ vaccination and exemption percentages and the odds of having a measles case.
COVERAGE ODDS RATIO P-VALUE
OVERALL VACCINATION 93-98% Ref
89-93% 5.36 0.113
83-89% 2.55 0.440
53-83% 0.89 0.944
MMR VACCINATION 95-100% Ref
92-95% 5.25 0.133
89-92% 3.23 0.327
71-89% 1.76 0.673
PERSONAL EXEMPTION 0.75-3% Ref
3-5.4% 6.02 0.086
5.4-7.1% 3.45 0.300
7.1-29.2% 1.00 1.00
MEDICAL EXEMPTION 0-0.5% Ref
0.5 – 2.0% 0.64 0.665
2-13.7% 0.59 0.555&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; 
Figure 1. Measles cases, vaccination coverage, and exemption percentages in the continental United States in 2019. Log,10 number of cases by state (A) and by county (B). Measles, mumps, and rubella (MMR) vaccination (C), personal exemption (D), medical exemption (E), and overall vaccination (F) percentages range between 0 and 100%. Grey = no data.
 
Figure 2. Measles cases, vaccination coverage, and exemption percentages in the Northwestern United States in 2019. Measles, mumps, and rubella (MMR) vaccination (A), personal exemption (B), medical exemption (C), and overall vaccination (D) percentages range between 0 and 100%. Log,10 number of cases by county (E). Red outline = counties with measles cases. Grey = no data.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DNV COBRA Vaccine Selection</title>
      <link>https://academic-demo.netlify.app/project/dengue-cartography/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://academic-demo.netlify.app/project/dengue-cartography/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;script src=&#34;https://academic-demo.netlify.app/project/dengue-cartography/index_files/header-attrs/header-attrs.js&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;script src=&#34;https://academic-demo.netlify.app/project/dengue-cartography/index_files/htmlwidgets/htmlwidgets.js&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;script src=&#34;https://academic-demo.netlify.app/project/dengue-cartography/index_files/plotly-binding/plotly.js&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;script src=&#34;https://academic-demo.netlify.app/project/dengue-cartography/index_files/typedarray/typedarray.min.js&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;script src=&#34;https://academic-demo.netlify.app/project/dengue-cartography/index_files/jquery/jquery.min.js&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;link href=&#34;https://academic-demo.netlify.app/project/dengue-cartography/index_files/crosstalk/css/crosstalk.css&#34; rel=&#34;stylesheet&#34; /&gt;
&lt;script src=&#34;https://academic-demo.netlify.app/project/dengue-cartography/index_files/crosstalk/js/crosstalk.min.js&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;link href=&#34;https://academic-demo.netlify.app/project/dengue-cartography/index_files/plotly-htmlwidgets-css/plotly-htmlwidgets.css&#34; rel=&#34;stylesheet&#34; /&gt;
&lt;script src=&#34;https://academic-demo.netlify.app/project/dengue-cartography/index_files/plotly-main/plotly-latest.min.js&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;


&lt;div id=&#34;htmlwidget-1&#34; style=&#34;width:672px;height:480px;&#34; class=&#34;plotly html-widget&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;script type=&#34;application/json&#34; data-for=&#34;htmlwidget-1&#34;&gt;{&#34;x&#34;:{&#34;visdat&#34;:{&#34;728d227b00df&#34;:[&#34;function () &#34;,&#34;plotlyVisDat&#34;]},&#34;cur_data&#34;:&#34;728d227b00df&#34;,&#34;attrs&#34;:{&#34;728d227b00df&#34;:{&#34;x&#34;:{},&#34;y&#34;:{},&#34;z&#34;:{},&#34;text&#34;:{},&#34;color&#34;:{},&#34;alpha_stroke&#34;:1,&#34;sizes&#34;:[10,100],&#34;spans&#34;:[1,20],&#34;type&#34;:&#34;scatter3d&#34;,&#34;mode&#34;:&#34;markers&#34;,&#34;symbol&#34;:{},&#34;symbols&#34;:[&#34;circle&#34;,&#34;square&#34;],&#34;inherit&#34;:true},&#34;728d227b00df.1&#34;:{&#34;x&#34;:{},&#34;y&#34;:{},&#34;z&#34;:{},&#34;text&#34;:{},&#34;color&#34;:{},&#34;alpha_stroke&#34;:1,&#34;sizes&#34;:[10,100],&#34;spans&#34;:[1,20],&#34;type&#34;:&#34;scatter3d&#34;,&#34;mode&#34;:&#34;text&#34;,&#34;inherit&#34;:true}},&#34;layout&#34;:{&#34;margin&#34;:{&#34;b&#34;:40,&#34;l&#34;:60,&#34;t&#34;:25,&#34;r&#34;:10},&#34;title&#34;:&#34;Dengue Antigens/Sera in 3D Space: Stress = 74.77&#34;,&#34;scene&#34;:{&#34;xaxis&#34;:{&#34;title&#34;:&#34;Antigenic Distance Unit&#34;},&#34;yaxis&#34;:{&#34;title&#34;:&#34;Antigenic Distance Unit&#34;},&#34;zaxis&#34;:{&#34;title&#34;:&#34;Antigenic Distance Unit&#34;}},&#34;hovermode&#34;:&#34;closest&#34;,&#34;showlegend&#34;:true},&#34;source&#34;:&#34;A&#34;,&#34;config&#34;:{&#34;showSendToCloud&#34;:false},&#34;data&#34;:[{&#34;x&#34;:[0.796106518078437,0.351520898477079,-1.25825358627161,-4.01017821032453],&#34;y&#34;:[1.58714591224027,-2.41000662702293,0.811957379295027,1.64419792518229],&#34;z&#34;:[0.535585840842574,1.12763861863607,-1.77212804016156,2.07024708245659],&#34;text&#34;:[&#34;COBRA 1&#34;,&#34;COBRA 2&#34;,&#34;COBRA 3&#34;,&#34;COBRA 4&#34;],&#34;type&#34;:&#34;scatter3d&#34;,&#34;mode&#34;:&#34;markers&#34;,&#34;name&#34;:&#34;COBRA&lt;br /&gt;sera&#34;,&#34;marker&#34;:{&#34;color&#34;:&#34;rgba(102,194,165,1)&#34;,&#34;symbol&#34;:&#34;square&#34;,&#34;line&#34;:{&#34;color&#34;:&#34;rgba(102,194,165,1)&#34;}},&#34;textfont&#34;:{&#34;color&#34;:&#34;rgba(102,194,165,1)&#34;},&#34;error_y&#34;:{&#34;color&#34;:&#34;rgba(102,194,165,1)&#34;},&#34;error_x&#34;:{&#34;color&#34;:&#34;rgba(102,194,165,1)&#34;},&#34;line&#34;:{&#34;color&#34;:&#34;rgba(102,194,165,1)&#34;},&#34;frame&#34;:null},{&#34;x&#34;:[1.39806143665463,2.368339017953,1.13469612757862],&#34;y&#34;:[3.58212618704867,2.34161204149525,3.29015449546967],&#34;z&#34;:[-0.349014724307742,0.917163415713673,-0.217217007514318],&#34;text&#34;:[&#34;Hawaii&#34;,&#34;American&#34;,&#34;Asian&#34;],&#34;type&#34;:&#34;scatter3d&#34;,&#34;mode&#34;:&#34;markers&#34;,&#34;name&#34;:&#34;DV1&lt;br /&gt;antigen&#34;,&#34;marker&#34;:{&#34;color&#34;:&#34;rgba(252,141,98,1)&#34;,&#34;symbol&#34;:&#34;circle&#34;,&#34;line&#34;:{&#34;color&#34;:&#34;rgba(252,141,98,1)&#34;}},&#34;textfont&#34;:{&#34;color&#34;:&#34;rgba(252,141,98,1)&#34;},&#34;error_y&#34;:{&#34;color&#34;:&#34;rgba(252,141,98,1)&#34;},&#34;error_x&#34;:{&#34;color&#34;:&#34;rgba(252,141,98,1)&#34;},&#34;line&#34;:{&#34;color&#34;:&#34;rgba(252,141,98,1)&#34;},&#34;frame&#34;:null},{&#34;x&#34;:[3.38519802975969],&#34;y&#34;:[1.54078739047182],&#34;z&#34;:[1.08427035011732],&#34;text&#34;:&#34;Hawaii&#34;,&#34;type&#34;:&#34;scatter3d&#34;,&#34;mode&#34;:&#34;markers&#34;,&#34;name&#34;:&#34;DV1&lt;br /&gt;sera&#34;,&#34;marker&#34;:{&#34;color&#34;:&#34;rgba(252,141,98,1)&#34;,&#34;symbol&#34;:&#34;square&#34;,&#34;line&#34;:{&#34;color&#34;:&#34;rgba(252,141,98,1)&#34;}},&#34;textfont&#34;:{&#34;color&#34;:&#34;rgba(252,141,98,1)&#34;},&#34;error_y&#34;:{&#34;color&#34;:&#34;rgba(252,141,98,1)&#34;},&#34;error_x&#34;:{&#34;color&#34;:&#34;rgba(252,141,98,1)&#34;},&#34;line&#34;:{&#34;color&#34;:&#34;rgba(252,141,98,1)&#34;},&#34;frame&#34;:null},{&#34;x&#34;:[1.04105079336964,0.819482930702842,0.557050206990874],&#34;y&#34;:[-0.953938781150294,-1.11778655365321,0.291215082738611],&#34;z&#34;:[3.60514390581775,0.963973298579253,2.02803211764276],&#34;text&#34;:[&#34;NGC&#34;,&#34;American&#34;,&#34;Asian&#34;],&#34;type&#34;:&#34;scatter3d&#34;,&#34;mode&#34;:&#34;markers&#34;,&#34;name&#34;:&#34;DV2&lt;br /&gt;antigen&#34;,&#34;marker&#34;:{&#34;color&#34;:&#34;rgba(141,160,203,1)&#34;,&#34;symbol&#34;:&#34;circle&#34;,&#34;line&#34;:{&#34;color&#34;:&#34;rgba(141,160,203,1)&#34;}},&#34;textfont&#34;:{&#34;color&#34;:&#34;rgba(141,160,203,1)&#34;},&#34;error_y&#34;:{&#34;color&#34;:&#34;rgba(141,160,203,1)&#34;},&#34;error_x&#34;:{&#34;color&#34;:&#34;rgba(141,160,203,1)&#34;},&#34;line&#34;:{&#34;color&#34;:&#34;rgba(141,160,203,1)&#34;},&#34;frame&#34;:null},{&#34;x&#34;:[-0.609115554270134],&#34;y&#34;:[1.01880146892839],&#34;z&#34;:[1.1182063354018],&#34;text&#34;:&#34;NGC&#34;,&#34;type&#34;:&#34;scatter3d&#34;,&#34;mode&#34;:&#34;markers&#34;,&#34;name&#34;:&#34;DV2&lt;br /&gt;sera&#34;,&#34;marker&#34;:{&#34;color&#34;:&#34;rgba(141,160,203,1)&#34;,&#34;symbol&#34;:&#34;square&#34;,&#34;line&#34;:{&#34;color&#34;:&#34;rgba(141,160,203,1)&#34;}},&#34;textfont&#34;:{&#34;color&#34;:&#34;rgba(141,160,203,1)&#34;},&#34;error_y&#34;:{&#34;color&#34;:&#34;rgba(141,160,203,1)&#34;},&#34;error_x&#34;:{&#34;color&#34;:&#34;rgba(141,160,203,1)&#34;},&#34;line&#34;:{&#34;color&#34;:&#34;rgba(141,160,203,1)&#34;},&#34;frame&#34;:null},{&#34;x&#34;:[-0.399211866962249,-0.304172489548584,-1.09298922175702],&#34;y&#34;:[0.0379147557881392,0.178410576156966,2.34717962581399],&#34;z&#34;:[-2.10980835043434,-2.02296573421157,-2.56280749177942],&#34;text&#34;:[&#34;H87&#34;,&#34;American&#34;,&#34;Asian&#34;],&#34;type&#34;:&#34;scatter3d&#34;,&#34;mode&#34;:&#34;markers&#34;,&#34;name&#34;:&#34;DV3&lt;br /&gt;antigen&#34;,&#34;marker&#34;:{&#34;color&#34;:&#34;rgba(231,138,195,1)&#34;,&#34;symbol&#34;:&#34;circle&#34;,&#34;line&#34;:{&#34;color&#34;:&#34;rgba(231,138,195,1)&#34;}},&#34;textfont&#34;:{&#34;color&#34;:&#34;rgba(231,138,195,1)&#34;},&#34;error_y&#34;:{&#34;color&#34;:&#34;rgba(231,138,195,1)&#34;},&#34;error_x&#34;:{&#34;color&#34;:&#34;rgba(231,138,195,1)&#34;},&#34;line&#34;:{&#34;color&#34;:&#34;rgba(231,138,195,1)&#34;},&#34;frame&#34;:null},{&#34;x&#34;:[-0.496628375088577],&#34;y&#34;:[-1.08548582561947],&#34;z&#34;:[-2.40786333175202],&#34;text&#34;:&#34;H87&#34;,&#34;type&#34;:&#34;scatter3d&#34;,&#34;mode&#34;:&#34;markers&#34;,&#34;name&#34;:&#34;DV3&lt;br /&gt;sera&#34;,&#34;marker&#34;:{&#34;color&#34;:&#34;rgba(231,138,195,1)&#34;,&#34;symbol&#34;:&#34;square&#34;,&#34;line&#34;:{&#34;color&#34;:&#34;rgba(231,138,195,1)&#34;}},&#34;textfont&#34;:{&#34;color&#34;:&#34;rgba(231,138,195,1)&#34;},&#34;error_y&#34;:{&#34;color&#34;:&#34;rgba(231,138,195,1)&#34;},&#34;error_x&#34;:{&#34;color&#34;:&#34;rgba(231,138,195,1)&#34;},&#34;line&#34;:{&#34;color&#34;:&#34;rgba(231,138,195,1)&#34;},&#34;frame&#34;:null},{&#34;x&#34;:[-3.09201242876377,-2.6575451371647,-2.78666376162756],&#34;y&#34;:[1.15955961580425,2.27537090278271,1.47114415674746],&#34;z&#34;:[1.66556171557522,2.77451780528911,1.22998706728569],&#34;text&#34;:[&#34;H241&#34;,&#34;American&#34;,&#34;Asian&#34;],&#34;type&#34;:&#34;scatter3d&#34;,&#34;mode&#34;:&#34;markers&#34;,&#34;name&#34;:&#34;DV4&lt;br /&gt;antigen&#34;,&#34;marker&#34;:{&#34;color&#34;:&#34;rgba(166,216,84,1)&#34;,&#34;symbol&#34;:&#34;circle&#34;,&#34;line&#34;:{&#34;color&#34;:&#34;rgba(166,216,84,1)&#34;}},&#34;textfont&#34;:{&#34;color&#34;:&#34;rgba(166,216,84,1)&#34;},&#34;error_y&#34;:{&#34;color&#34;:&#34;rgba(166,216,84,1)&#34;},&#34;error_x&#34;:{&#34;color&#34;:&#34;rgba(166,216,84,1)&#34;},&#34;line&#34;:{&#34;color&#34;:&#34;rgba(166,216,84,1)&#34;},&#34;frame&#34;:null},{&#34;x&#34;:[-4.64014331477733],&#34;y&#34;:[1.07769955381881],&#34;z&#34;:[2.33509194374514],&#34;text&#34;:&#34;H241&#34;,&#34;type&#34;:&#34;scatter3d&#34;,&#34;mode&#34;:&#34;markers&#34;,&#34;name&#34;:&#34;DV4&lt;br /&gt;sera&#34;,&#34;marker&#34;:{&#34;color&#34;:&#34;rgba(166,216,84,1)&#34;,&#34;symbol&#34;:&#34;square&#34;,&#34;line&#34;:{&#34;color&#34;:&#34;rgba(166,216,84,1)&#34;}},&#34;textfont&#34;:{&#34;color&#34;:&#34;rgba(166,216,84,1)&#34;},&#34;error_y&#34;:{&#34;color&#34;:&#34;rgba(166,216,84,1)&#34;},&#34;error_x&#34;:{&#34;color&#34;:&#34;rgba(166,216,84,1)&#34;},&#34;line&#34;:{&#34;color&#34;:&#34;rgba(166,216,84,1)&#34;},&#34;frame&#34;:null},{&#34;x&#34;:[0.796106518078437,0.351520898477079,-1.25825358627161,-4.01017821032453],&#34;y&#34;:[1.58714591224027,-2.41000662702293,0.811957379295027,1.64419792518229],&#34;z&#34;:[0.535585840842574,1.12763861863607,-1.77212804016156,2.07024708245659],&#34;text&#34;:[&#34;COBRA 1&#34;,&#34;COBRA 2&#34;,&#34;COBRA 3&#34;,&#34;COBRA 4&#34;],&#34;type&#34;:&#34;scatter3d&#34;,&#34;mode&#34;:&#34;text&#34;,&#34;name&#34;:&#34;COBRA&#34;,&#34;marker&#34;:{&#34;color&#34;:&#34;rgba(102,194,165,1)&#34;,&#34;line&#34;:{&#34;color&#34;:&#34;rgba(102,194,165,1)&#34;}},&#34;textfont&#34;:{&#34;color&#34;:&#34;rgba(102,194,165,1)&#34;},&#34;error_y&#34;:{&#34;color&#34;:&#34;rgba(102,194,165,1)&#34;},&#34;error_x&#34;:{&#34;color&#34;:&#34;rgba(102,194,165,1)&#34;},&#34;line&#34;:{&#34;color&#34;:&#34;rgba(102,194,165,1)&#34;},&#34;frame&#34;:null},{&#34;x&#34;:[1.39806143665463,2.368339017953,1.13469612757862,3.38519802975969],&#34;y&#34;:[3.58212618704867,2.34161204149525,3.29015449546967,1.54078739047182],&#34;z&#34;:[-0.349014724307742,0.917163415713673,-0.217217007514318,1.08427035011732],&#34;text&#34;:[&#34;Hawaii&#34;,&#34;American&#34;,&#34;Asian&#34;,&#34;Hawaii&#34;],&#34;type&#34;:&#34;scatter3d&#34;,&#34;mode&#34;:&#34;text&#34;,&#34;name&#34;:&#34;DV1&#34;,&#34;marker&#34;:{&#34;color&#34;:&#34;rgba(252,141,98,1)&#34;,&#34;line&#34;:{&#34;color&#34;:&#34;rgba(252,141,98,1)&#34;}},&#34;textfont&#34;:{&#34;color&#34;:&#34;rgba(252,141,98,1)&#34;},&#34;error_y&#34;:{&#34;color&#34;:&#34;rgba(252,141,98,1)&#34;},&#34;error_x&#34;:{&#34;color&#34;:&#34;rgba(252,141,98,1)&#34;},&#34;line&#34;:{&#34;color&#34;:&#34;rgba(252,141,98,1)&#34;},&#34;frame&#34;:null},{&#34;x&#34;:[1.04105079336964,0.819482930702842,0.557050206990874,-0.609115554270134],&#34;y&#34;:[-0.953938781150294,-1.11778655365321,0.291215082738611,1.01880146892839],&#34;z&#34;:[3.60514390581775,0.963973298579253,2.02803211764276,1.1182063354018],&#34;text&#34;:[&#34;NGC&#34;,&#34;American&#34;,&#34;Asian&#34;,&#34;NGC&#34;],&#34;type&#34;:&#34;scatter3d&#34;,&#34;mode&#34;:&#34;text&#34;,&#34;name&#34;:&#34;DV2&#34;,&#34;marker&#34;:{&#34;color&#34;:&#34;rgba(141,160,203,1)&#34;,&#34;line&#34;:{&#34;color&#34;:&#34;rgba(141,160,203,1)&#34;}},&#34;textfont&#34;:{&#34;color&#34;:&#34;rgba(141,160,203,1)&#34;},&#34;error_y&#34;:{&#34;color&#34;:&#34;rgba(141,160,203,1)&#34;},&#34;error_x&#34;:{&#34;color&#34;:&#34;rgba(141,160,203,1)&#34;},&#34;line&#34;:{&#34;color&#34;:&#34;rgba(141,160,203,1)&#34;},&#34;frame&#34;:null},{&#34;x&#34;:[-0.399211866962249,-0.304172489548584,-1.09298922175702,-0.496628375088577],&#34;y&#34;:[0.0379147557881392,0.178410576156966,2.34717962581399,-1.08548582561947],&#34;z&#34;:[-2.10980835043434,-2.02296573421157,-2.56280749177942,-2.40786333175202],&#34;text&#34;:[&#34;H87&#34;,&#34;American&#34;,&#34;Asian&#34;,&#34;H87&#34;],&#34;type&#34;:&#34;scatter3d&#34;,&#34;mode&#34;:&#34;text&#34;,&#34;name&#34;:&#34;DV3&#34;,&#34;marker&#34;:{&#34;color&#34;:&#34;rgba(231,138,195,1)&#34;,&#34;line&#34;:{&#34;color&#34;:&#34;rgba(231,138,195,1)&#34;}},&#34;textfont&#34;:{&#34;color&#34;:&#34;rgba(231,138,195,1)&#34;},&#34;error_y&#34;:{&#34;color&#34;:&#34;rgba(231,138,195,1)&#34;},&#34;error_x&#34;:{&#34;color&#34;:&#34;rgba(231,138,195,1)&#34;},&#34;line&#34;:{&#34;color&#34;:&#34;rgba(231,138,195,1)&#34;},&#34;frame&#34;:null},{&#34;x&#34;:[-3.09201242876377,-2.6575451371647,-2.78666376162756,-4.64014331477733],&#34;y&#34;:[1.15955961580425,2.27537090278271,1.47114415674746,1.07769955381881],&#34;z&#34;:[1.66556171557522,2.77451780528911,1.22998706728569,2.33509194374514],&#34;text&#34;:[&#34;H241&#34;,&#34;American&#34;,&#34;Asian&#34;,&#34;H241&#34;],&#34;type&#34;:&#34;scatter3d&#34;,&#34;mode&#34;:&#34;text&#34;,&#34;name&#34;:&#34;DV4&#34;,&#34;marker&#34;:{&#34;color&#34;:&#34;rgba(166,216,84,1)&#34;,&#34;line&#34;:{&#34;color&#34;:&#34;rgba(166,216,84,1)&#34;}},&#34;textfont&#34;:{&#34;color&#34;:&#34;rgba(166,216,84,1)&#34;},&#34;error_y&#34;:{&#34;color&#34;:&#34;rgba(166,216,84,1)&#34;},&#34;error_x&#34;:{&#34;color&#34;:&#34;rgba(166,216,84,1)&#34;},&#34;line&#34;:{&#34;color&#34;:&#34;rgba(166,216,84,1)&#34;},&#34;frame&#34;:null}],&#34;highlight&#34;:{&#34;on&#34;:&#34;plotly_click&#34;,&#34;persistent&#34;:false,&#34;dynamic&#34;:false,&#34;selectize&#34;:false,&#34;opacityDim&#34;:0.2,&#34;selected&#34;:{&#34;opacity&#34;:1},&#34;debounce&#34;:0},&#34;shinyEvents&#34;:[&#34;plotly_hover&#34;,&#34;plotly_click&#34;,&#34;plotly_selected&#34;,&#34;plotly_relayout&#34;,&#34;plotly_brushed&#34;,&#34;plotly_brushing&#34;,&#34;plotly_clickannotation&#34;,&#34;plotly_doubleclick&#34;,&#34;plotly_deselect&#34;,&#34;plotly_afterplot&#34;,&#34;plotly_sunburstclick&#34;],&#34;base_url&#34;:&#34;https://plot.ly&#34;},&#34;evals&#34;:[],&#34;jsHooks&#34;:[]}&lt;/script&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Internal Project</title>
      <link>https://academic-demo.netlify.app/project/internal-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://academic-demo.netlify.app/project/internal-project/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit. Duis posuere tellus ac convallis placerat. Proin tincidunt magna sed ex sollicitudin condimentum. Sed ac faucibus dolor, scelerisque sollicitudin nisi. Cras purus urna, suscipit quis sapien eu, pulvinar tempor diam. Quisque risus orci, mollis id ante sit amet, gravida egestas nisl. Sed ac tempus magna. Proin in dui enim. Donec condimentum, sem id dapibus fringilla, tellus enim condimentum arcu, nec volutpat est felis vel metus. Vestibulum sit amet erat at nulla eleifend gravida.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nullam vel molestie justo. Curabitur vitae efficitur leo. In hac habitasse platea dictumst. Sed pulvinar mauris dui, eget varius purus congue ac. Nulla euismod, lorem vel elementum dapibus, nunc justo porta mi, sed tempus est est vel tellus. Nam et enim eleifend, laoreet sem sit amet, elementum sem. Morbi ut leo congue, maximus velit ut, finibus arcu. In et libero cursus, rutrum risus non, molestie leo. Nullam congue quam et volutpat malesuada. Sed risus tortor, pulvinar et dictum nec, sodales non mi. Phasellus lacinia commodo laoreet. Nam mollis, erat in feugiat consectetur, purus eros egestas tellus, in auctor urna odio at nibh. Mauris imperdiet nisi ac magna convallis, at rhoncus ligula cursus.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cras aliquam rhoncus ipsum, in hendrerit nunc mattis vitae. Duis vitae efficitur metus, ac tempus leo. Cras nec fringilla lacus. Quisque sit amet risus at ipsum pharetra commodo. Sed aliquam mauris at consequat eleifend. Praesent porta, augue sed viverra bibendum, neque ante euismod ante, in vehicula justo lorem ac eros. Suspendisse augue libero, venenatis eget tincidunt ut, malesuada at lorem. Donec vitae bibendum arcu. Aenean maximus nulla non pretium iaculis. Quisque imperdiet, nulla in pulvinar aliquet, velit quam ultrices quam, sit amet fringilla leo sem vel nunc. Mauris in lacinia lacus.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Suspendisse a tincidunt lacus. Curabitur at urna sagittis, dictum ante sit amet, euismod magna. Sed rutrum massa id tortor commodo, vitae elementum turpis tempus. Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit. Aenean purus turpis, venenatis a ullamcorper nec, tincidunt et massa. Integer posuere quam rutrum arcu vehicula imperdiet. Mauris ullamcorper quam vitae purus congue, quis euismod magna eleifend. Vestibulum semper vel augue eget tincidunt. Fusce eget justo sodales, dapibus odio eu, ultrices lorem. Duis condimentum lorem id eros commodo, in facilisis mauris scelerisque. Morbi sed auctor leo. Nullam volutpat a lacus quis pharetra. Nulla congue rutrum magna a ornare.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Aliquam in turpis accumsan, malesuada nibh ut, hendrerit justo. Cum sociis natoque penatibus et magnis dis parturient montes, nascetur ridiculus mus. Quisque sed erat nec justo posuere suscipit. Donec ut efficitur arcu, in malesuada neque. Nunc dignissim nisl massa, id vulputate nunc pretium nec. Quisque eget urna in risus suscipit ultricies. Pellentesque odio odio, tincidunt in eleifend sed, posuere a diam. Nam gravida nisl convallis semper elementum. Morbi vitae felis faucibus, vulputate orci placerat, aliquet nisi. Aliquam erat volutpat. Maecenas sagittis pulvinar purus, sed porta quam laoreet at.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
